<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Life &#8211; End World Hunger 2045 &#8211; Endworldhunger2045.com</title>
	<atom:link href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/category/life/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://endworldhunger2045.com/</link>
	<description>End World Hunger 2045 is a foundation dedicated to helping provide those in need with life&#039;s basic necessities food, clothing, access to employment.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 01:20:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.9</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/cropped-FAVICON-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Life &#8211; End World Hunger 2045 &#8211; Endworldhunger2045.com</title>
	<link>https://endworldhunger2045.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>What is all about?</title>
		<link>https://endworldhunger2045.com/what-is-all-about/</link>
				<comments>https://endworldhunger2045.com/what-is-all-about/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 01:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[fund.ewh2045@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://endworldhunger2045.com/?p=2617</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>I started out in life so carefree and happy. I was like a little butterfly with beautiful wings and a world of flowers to see. Life seemed wonderful as I looked to the future. It didn't take long and my views changed. I realized I had to perform to be accepted. Life seemed like a &#91;...&#93;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/what-is-all-about/">What is all about?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I started out in life so carefree and happy. I was like a little butterfly with beautiful wings and a world of flowers to see. Life seemed wonderful as I looked to the future.</p>
<p>It didn&#8217;t take long and my views changed. I realized I had to perform to be accepted. Life seemed like a circus. There were hoops held out far into the future. If I jumped through the rings I received approval. If I didn&#8217;t -well-everybody else did</p>
<p>Life become a performance. Leap through the rings; make the football team, or the cheer-leading squad, or to the honor roll. Go to the right college and get a degree, I did somethings I wished I hadn&#8217;t, but everyone else did them &#8211; so -go- on and hope to forget. Get a good job and make lots of money. At the right time get married, have the correct number of children, buy a house-a nice big house, a a better car. I think I&#8217;m getting tired. Join the club &#8211; jump, jump, jump. Retirement, I have to think about retirement-buy stock, sell stocks-hit some bumps, go, go, go.</p>
<p>And suddenly, I stand before the last hoop. But it isn&#8217;t round, it&#8217;s rectangular, and it&#8217;s in the ground. The grass stops at the ragged edges. Here is where it all ends.</p>
<p>What happened to me anyways? Life wasn&#8217;t supposed to be this way. Where is the little butterfly with the beautiful wings? What happened to the flowers? Was I truly happy? What about my soul? Is this what is all about?</p>
<p>&#8220;God, what happened?&#8221;</p>
<p>Reflect on it often to find the truth and change the course of your life. Happiness and fulfillment is not hard to find if you put effort to look deep inside and ask right questions</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/what-is-all-about/">What is all about?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://endworldhunger2045.com/what-is-all-about/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Welcoming Party in Arusha, Tanzania</title>
		<link>https://endworldhunger2045.com/welcoming-party-in-arusha-tanzania/</link>
				<comments>https://endworldhunger2045.com/welcoming-party-in-arusha-tanzania/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 10:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[fund.ewh2045@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://endworldhunger2045.com/?p=2596</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>With the help of our local coordinator Shimba as well as many volunteers, End World Hunger 2045 organized on March 24, 2019 a get together with all of the orphan children in Arusha, Tanzania. The food was served and children had time to socialize and play together. We at End World Hunger 2045 have a &#91;...&#93;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/welcoming-party-in-arusha-tanzania/">Welcoming Party in Arusha, Tanzania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the help of our local coordinator Shimba as well as many volunteers, End World Hunger 2045 organized on March 24, 2019 a get together with all of the orphan children in Arusha, Tanzania. The food was served and children had time to socialize and play together. We at End World Hunger 2045 have a big responsibility to help these children provide basic necessities. We are looking for donors now to help with the building of new school. With support of many we can achieve a great humanitarian impact. Join us at #endworldhunger2045 to make a change in life of these children!</p>
<p>Watch video here: <a href="https://youtu.be/yRRJN83cIzQ">https://youtu.be/yRRJN83cIzQ</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img class="alignnone wp-image-2598 " src="https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/68cca563-3c6b-480c-80b1-249fd09cf19b-e1553509099752-300x225.jpg" alt="Orphans of Arusha, Tanzania holding plates of beans and rice indoors" width="401" height="301" srcset="https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/68cca563-3c6b-480c-80b1-249fd09cf19b-e1553509099752-200x150.jpg 200w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/68cca563-3c6b-480c-80b1-249fd09cf19b-e1553509099752-300x225.jpg 300w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/68cca563-3c6b-480c-80b1-249fd09cf19b-e1553509099752-400x300.jpg 400w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/68cca563-3c6b-480c-80b1-249fd09cf19b-e1553509099752-600x450.jpg 600w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/68cca563-3c6b-480c-80b1-249fd09cf19b-e1553509099752-768x576.jpg 768w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/68cca563-3c6b-480c-80b1-249fd09cf19b-e1553509099752-800x600.jpg 800w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/68cca563-3c6b-480c-80b1-249fd09cf19b-e1553509099752-1024x768.jpg 1024w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/68cca563-3c6b-480c-80b1-249fd09cf19b-e1553509099752.jpg 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 401px) 100vw, 401px" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/welcoming-party-in-arusha-tanzania/">Welcoming Party in Arusha, Tanzania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://endworldhunger2045.com/welcoming-party-in-arusha-tanzania/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Working With End World Hunger 2045</title>
		<link>https://endworldhunger2045.com/working-with-endworldhunger2045/</link>
				<comments>https://endworldhunger2045.com/working-with-endworldhunger2045/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 11:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[fund.ewh2045@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://endworldhunger2045.com/?p=2561</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>How can i describe my personal experience working with End World Hunger 2045? I cant. Like a parents love for their child, it can only be experienced not described until you have a child. or in my sense, until you work with End World Hunger 2045. My whole life i have been rejected and been &#91;...&#93;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/working-with-endworldhunger2045/">Working With End World Hunger 2045</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How can i describe my personal experience working with End World Hunger 2045? I cant. Like a parents love for their child, it can only be experienced not described until you have a child. or in my sense, until you work with End World Hunger 2045. My whole life i have been rejected and been looked down on. Was never smart enough, was never big enough, anything i tried to do i just never met the correct standards. I got accepted into this group of amazing people and got invited to work on this project, i can whole hardheartedly say I finally feel fully accepted for who i am. My motives to life itself have changed since working with the group in end world hunger. I am really looking forward to spreading awareness to this project so we can one day touch millions of lives across the globe. Not only I know me working within the project will help touch more lives, but whats more exciting is we are now using our personal passions, hobbies, and income for good &amp; not for selfish pleasures. We are able to use things like money as a tool to fix and not destroy. And if that is not called a good way to live life then i don&#8217;t know what is. When I look around at this world i see a need for help, immorality, selfishness, but i also see a beautiful bright side that needs to be brought out more. My mission here working in this project is to bring it out as far as my tools and influence can reach.</p>
<p>So how can i describe my personal experience with End World Hunger 2045? Let me just encourage you to go hand and hand with us on making a difference in the world and you can experience it for yourself. Moral of the story: &#8220;There are some things you can describe, and some things you can only experience.&#8221; The End World Hunger project is just one of those things that you can only experience to understand it fully.</p>
<p>Samuel Katallah,</p>
<p>AKA &#8211; <a href="https://www.instagram.com/samgottem/?hl=en">SamGottem</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/working-with-endworldhunger2045/">Working With End World Hunger 2045</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://endworldhunger2045.com/working-with-endworldhunger2045/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dream of a rapper</title>
		<link>https://endworldhunger2045.com/dream-of-a-rapper/</link>
				<comments>https://endworldhunger2045.com/dream-of-a-rapper/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 04:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[fund.ewh2045@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://endworldhunger2045.com/?p=2552</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever had a dream of doing something special in this world? What about doubts from everyone? How can you make your ideas reality? Is the God ever going to help me? This is what all of us are facing in many situations. Some of us have an easier life and others just don't &#91;...&#93;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/dream-of-a-rapper/">Dream of a rapper</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever had a dream of doing something special in this world? What about doubts from everyone? How can you make your ideas reality? Is the God ever going to help me? This is what all of us are facing in many situations. Some of us have an easier life and others just don&#8217;t get any breaks. The important moment is to be true to yourself and have kindness towards others. Patience with oneself and others. Have dedication to your craft and do it better every time, yet understand that perfection is in the eye of the beholder.</p>
<p>We are social creatures and need support and help from others. Listen to the heart but also listen to other and understand what is the message. The parents the siblings are closest people to us, yet we have most difficulties with them. We know our habits when we live together and find faults in other very easy. Our responsibility towards each other to guide and help but not interfere with others paths. Of course a mother will not let their child cross the busy street by himself or a baby to let touch a hot stove. When times comes in life from youth until old age we learn most from our mistakes. Be open to mistakes and the more you make them the more you will learn.</p>
<p>Dreams come in a time when new idea sprout, when change is encouraged! Dream big, universe whats you to dream to set big visions. When visions are inline with our purpose in life they will happen. The harder it gets the sweeter the results are. Easy come, easy go. Remember in life we will have hard times and that will teach us a lot. We build our stamina of difficulty, we create a internal strength where nothing will crush our dreams. We keep focused on vision with the right actions to follow. Respect others in the process, associate with the sincere and dedicated people, do not accept carelessness and heedlessness.</p>
<p>You will be able to achieve your dream once life will not be taken for granted. Enjoy the life in any form. Be content with situations and breathe when times are difficult. Have respect for yourself and others. Music and words are helping us to create. The purpose of arts is to connect with the divine. Artists have a very task to create when they understand suffering the most. They are on a mission to show the rest how tolerance works. Respect for artist as their mission in this world is not easy.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2553" src="https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_8379.jpg" alt="" width="665" height="619" srcset="https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_8379-200x186.jpg 200w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_8379-300x279.jpg 300w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_8379-400x372.jpg 400w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_8379-600x558.jpg 600w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_8379.jpg 665w" sizes="(max-width: 665px) 100vw, 665px" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/dream-of-a-rapper/">Dream of a rapper</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://endworldhunger2045.com/dream-of-a-rapper/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
