<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mind &#8211; End World Hunger 2045 &#8211; Endworldhunger2045.com</title>
	<atom:link href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/category/mind/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://endworldhunger2045.com/</link>
	<description>End World Hunger 2045 is a foundation dedicated to helping provide those in need with life&#039;s basic necessities food, clothing, access to employment.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 01:03:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.9</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/cropped-FAVICON-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Mind &#8211; End World Hunger 2045 &#8211; Endworldhunger2045.com</title>
	<link>https://endworldhunger2045.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mindset change</title>
		<link>https://endworldhunger2045.com/mindset-change/</link>
				<comments>https://endworldhunger2045.com/mindset-change/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 09:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[fund.ewh2045@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Mind]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://endworldhunger2045.com/?p=2600</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>People's life is guided but different things, such us culture, greed and manifold others that may not allow individuals to get open to the world. Is this the reality in your community? Having a specific culture is not that bad in itself, however, when it sets some barriers as to what to do and what &#91;...&#93;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/mindset-change/">Mindset change</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>People&#8217;s life is guided but different things, such us culture, greed and manifold others that may not allow individuals to get open to the world. Is this the reality in your community? Having a specific culture is not that bad in itself, however, when it sets some barriers as to what to do and what no to be done but doable, it proves impeding. Some cultures are less limiting, anyone has his/her role to play in his own progress; People are masters of their own future and more often than not, it results in a huge progress not only at the individual level but at the nation level and most importantly if that was to be the conception for all, the world would look much better than it does. On the other hand, there are countries where life is programmed. It looks like there is a life routine that everyone has to follow just to appear pure to the community. It limits folks from dreaming and opening their eyes to know what happens elsewhere in the world, It has disadvantages to the society as it remains into the traditional practices and no development at all.</p>
<p>Some people also do stick to their greed which prevent them from some activities. Some people may even have hatred towards some other individuals whom they do not share the believing way. God does not oblige us to part ways with anyone despite his/her spiritual belief, we are created to work together, love each other and finally help one another. Delusion comes to distract us and we must get rid of it and learn to cooperate as much as we can.</p>
<p>Different societies that succeeded to evolve economically and socially started by changing people&#8217;s mindset. As <a href="https://stevemaraboli.net/">Steve Maraboli</a> mentions it, &#8220;once your mindset changes, everything on the outside will change along with it.&#8221; People get free to think and explore the world, something that gives good results for the world in general. It substantially brings happiness to everyone, &#8220;Happiness depends on your mindset and attitude&#8221;, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/roytbennettauthor/">Roy T. Bennett</a>.</p>
<p>In a nutshell, people should learn to be as positive as they can to harness their own future and happiness just through examining what they live in the community. Trying to install good values that value individuals and teach others to view the world as their place of joy should be everyone&#8217;s duty.</p>
<p>Written by Joseph Nimbona in Burundi.</p>
<p>Edited by Sergiu Kondanna in Rome</p>
<p><img class="alignnone wp-image-2346 size-medium" src="https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/END-WORLD-HUNGER-2045-225x300.jpg" alt="Joseph and Sergiu embracing each other with one hand and smiling" width="225" height="300" srcset="https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/END-WORLD-HUNGER-2045-200x267.jpg 200w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/END-WORLD-HUNGER-2045-225x300.jpg 225w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/END-WORLD-HUNGER-2045-400x533.jpg 400w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/END-WORLD-HUNGER-2045.jpg 525w" sizes="(max-width: 225px) 100vw, 225px" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/mindset-change/">Mindset change</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://endworldhunger2045.com/mindset-change/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dhamapada Reflections HAPPINESS</title>
		<link>https://endworldhunger2045.com/dhamapada-reflections-happiness/</link>
				<comments>https://endworldhunger2045.com/dhamapada-reflections-happiness/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 18:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[fund.ewh2045@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Mind]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://endworldhunger2045.com/?p=2554</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>While in the midst of those who are greedy, to dwell free from greed is happiness indeed! We hold values such as honesty, selfishness and generosity to be honorable. However, it can be hard to live our lives aligned with these values when most of those around us are traveling in a different direction. The &#91;...&#93;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/dhamapada-reflections-happiness/">Dhamapada Reflections HAPPINESS</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While in the midst of those who are greedy, to dwell free from greed is happiness indeed!</p>
<p>We hold values such as honesty, selfishness and generosity to be honorable. However, it can be hard to live our lives aligned with these values when most of those around us are traveling in a different direction. The Buddha knew it could be hard, but he says that to dwell thus in the source of happiness. If we betray ourselves to heedlessness, stop and feel the consequences. Don&#8217;t be be in a hurry to escape. Then imagine how the opposite might feel were we to hold to integrity. Likewise, consider how it feels to focus attention on feelings of gratitude instead of indulging in a sense of luck. Not adding anything to this moment or taking anything from it, we incline towards inner peace and contentment.  Establishing ourselves in this awareness, we are less likely to be intimidated by others.</p>
<p><a href="https://forestsangha.org/">Ajahn Munindo</a></p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-2555 size-full" src="https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/Ajahn-Munindo-e1550342896200.png" alt="Black and white Ajahn Munindo dressed in robes" width="277" height="208" srcset="https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/Ajahn-Munindo-e1550342896200-200x150.png 200w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/Ajahn-Munindo-e1550342896200.png 277w" sizes="(max-width: 277px) 100vw, 277px" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/dhamapada-reflections-happiness/">Dhamapada Reflections HAPPINESS</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://endworldhunger2045.com/dhamapada-reflections-happiness/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>MONEY IS NOT IMPORTANT!</title>
		<link>https://endworldhunger2045.com/money-is-not-important/</link>
				<comments>https://endworldhunger2045.com/money-is-not-important/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 02:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[fund.ewh2045@gmail.com]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Mind]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://endworldhunger2045.com/?p=2547</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>What is money? It is a tool, means of exchanging goods, a way to help us humans with our lives, to live well when we accumulate enough. Money is a way of helping others. We can live well with little money. We think only if we can have lot then we will be fulfilled. However, &#91;...&#93;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/money-is-not-important/">MONEY IS NOT IMPORTANT!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">What is money? It is a tool, means of exchanging goods, a way to help us humans with our lives, to live well when we accumulate enough. Money is a way of helping others. We can live well with little money. We think only if we can have lot then we will be fulfilled. However, ask any lottery winner. Did it change there lives for long once they got it? The reality is that the money is never the source of our happiness. It is the things we do that make us happy.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Now we have a choice. Money or fostering relationships? It is the people you interact with in the organization you work with or for that is the real source of happiness. When money comes, it will be joyful because we do what we love and earn money in the process. Money is secondary when the environment we operate in is not beneficial for our contentment with life, despite earning lots. Look deeply at the cause of the unhappiness and you will always find <a href="https://www.facebook.com/endworldhunger2045/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">money as secondary</a>.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">We trade time for money, and have none left to enjoy life. How much do you need to live life in full. Some of the most happy people are people with little. They figure out the way out of unhappy mind, realizing that money is secondary in life in every situation. Universe has its life path for everyone and no matter how much we push it away, suppress it and trying to run away from it is always there. The path of helping others is what we all are on this mother Earth come into existence. The service we can do comes in many forms, material when you have lots give to others, in the form of transferring the knowledge to other, in the form of protecting weak and needed.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">As humans we have the highest level of consciousness and can do wonders for rest of beings and our mother Earth when life is understood outside of money. Imagine no money available, how would we live today. Imagine how we can be more attentive and helpful to each other when all equal. One might say will never happen, but the time is here and now, the universal consciousness is giving us hints it can not continue in the way it was before. Big changes are happening as we speak, be ready to change, only ones with open mind will be able to live happy rest are bound to suffer.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Money will cease to exist once new ways of interchanging products and services will be in place and is coming soon. Be alert, be mindful and think about others, not just oneself. We are all one, humans, birds, animals, flowers, trees, mother Earth, father Sun, mysterious Universe. When some links are not working in our relationship with others the universe will adjust to ensure the right balance is in place and always guide us to what is the best to ensure Love and Peace is restored, because is ultimate goal is to ensure safety and service for all beings.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/pg/endworldhunger2045/about/"><img class="aligncenter wp-image-2548 size-medium" src="https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_4151-300x225.jpg" alt="Man wearing a shirt with the words hunger inspired me to give in front of a swimming pool in a hot place" width="300" height="225" srcset="https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_4151-200x150.jpg 200w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_4151-300x225.jpg 300w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_4151-400x300.jpg 400w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_4151-600x450.jpg 600w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_4151-768x576.jpg 768w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_4151-800x600.jpg 800w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_4151-1024x768.jpg 1024w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_4151-1200x900.jpg 1200w, https://endworldhunger2045.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/IMG_4151.jpg 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/money-is-not-important/">MONEY IS NOT IMPORTANT!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://endworldhunger2045.com/">End World Hunger 2045 - Endworldhunger2045.com</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://endworldhunger2045.com/money-is-not-important/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
